Hello friends, hello friends, welcome to
our channel Tech N friends, in today's
video we will tell you that if you are also
a CSC and friends, if you also
want to do two wheeler insurance from the digital service portals of CSC or friends, then
friends, in this video we will tell you that
which is a digital company which
provides two wheeler and four wheeler insurance service, friends,
in this video we will tell you that the date of two
wheeler insurance is
of first party, then friends, if you do two wheeler
insurance of first party, then
how much commission do you get in it, how much
percentage commission do you get, in this video we will
show you the details which are live, friends, along with the information, many
friends on YouTube, many of their
CSC officials claim that they
get 20% 18% commission in CSC, so friends, the wrong claim is
absolutely wrong, in this video we are going to
give you complete information and
friends, we
will show you the details with full proof that  In that date, how much commission does CSC also get in the first
party two wheeler insurance,
friends, we can see here on the
Detersewa portal, we have
logged in here and friends, here
friends, here we have gone to the order history,
we can see the order here,
friends, here on 28th April itself,
we did an insurance, two
wheeler insurance, which was
digital's first party, so you
can see there, friends, the order
total here, friends, is of Rs 2408, which
means friends, the
customer had to pay Rs 248 for the insurance
and friends, you can see here, then
from here we go to the details,
so let's click on details,
friends, here you will see the complete details, you can
see here, the
name of the service is Motor Compressor, friends, here
this is the first party
and the name of the merchant is like God Digital Gender
Insurance Limited
34 paisa and friends, our
balance detector from CSC is not done, friends  The
debit that has happened is
214 61 friends now if we talk about earning
i.e. commission then here we
can see that our commission is
277 and friends our TDS
is also ₹1388 which has been taken in this so
friends you can see that it is live here here
so friends if we
talk about its commission then if we calculate its
percentage then friends the
percentage that comes out is
11 point friends 11.5 here we are
calculating the percentage so 11 point is
what you get five you
can calculate its percentage and give it in this
friends it comes in the bigger of 276 so
friends here you get 11.5%
commission if we do
first
party two wheeler insurance from the general insurance company of digital so
friends this is how its insurance
is and rest friends I do
not know about third party, I have never done third party in this
but friends if you board any then if any
customer comes to you  It comes
and if you do that digitally, then
friends, your
11.30 percent commission is going to be made,
friends, in this video we were going to give you
big information about this, friends,
if you liked the video then
like the video and if you have come to our channel for the first
time then do not forget to subscribe to the channel.